The best revenge is to be beautiful.
And the best place to be beautiful
is at the Grand Gyronella University Ball.
Don't experiment on me.
But you're our friend, Florence.
Friends help each other.
Friends are always there for each other.
And friends party together!
Friends always offer a helping hand.
And when you get murdered,
we, your friends, will avenge your death.
True.
You're overreacting with the murder part.
So, game?
So, will you be my date?
Don't you have any other choice?
This is it, guys.
Welcome to this year's Grand Gyronella Ball.
A celebration of humanity and beauty.
And it looks like the king and queen
have arrived.
Here we have
Ms. Antonia Scarlet Vamorida Fuentes,
escorted by none other
than Nero Sebastian Araneta Ferell.
Antonia looks perfect in her sparkly,
like-a-night-filled-with-stars dress.
I think that's how I would be describing it.
Florence?
Can we just talk?
No need.
I don't want people to see me.
I look like a fool.
Come on, Florence, it can't be that bad.
Please, Owen, this is not me.
You'll all laugh at me once you see me.
I just want to see you and who knows,
maybe Ma'am Serafica and I can help you.
Okay, thank you for the update.
What's happening?
Is Florence okay?
It seems she's not happy
with how she turned out earlier,
that's why the stylist said
she might not come.
Huh?
It can't be that bad.
Wow!
That is crazy, bro!
I'm not going to lie, they look good.
Don Ferell, Don Rogelio, excuse me.
Yeah.
Grandpa.
Owen, and of course
our beautiful Princess, Florence.
Give your Grandpa Garp a kiss.
It's nice to see you
in a different light, Florence.
And of course, your accessory is perfect.
Hi, Florence.
Hello, Don Rogelio.
I'm sorry I didn't notice that you were here.
It was nice hanging out with you
the other day.
Hanging out?
Yes, we saw each other
at Mr. Henry's chicken.
That's one of Florence's favorite places.
And I apologized to her about what happened.
And somehow, we were able to talk.
Yes, Grandpa Garp.
And Don Rogelio is also cool.
And I envy you, Garpidio.
You found a great cook in her.
And from what I sense here,
you bring a lot of positive energy
and happiness.
She is special,
and I'm glad we got to know her.
I'm sorry the music is on...
Owen, do you mind if I dance with Florence?
Go ahead. Go ahead, sir.
Do you like that guy, Owen?
What? Owen?
We're just friends.
When I look into your eyes, I see love.
What makes you say that?
I once fell in love...
and I know it when I see it.
What do I know about love?
Love is complicated...
but if there's one advice I can give you,
it is to listen to your heart
because your heart tells the truth.
Our heart is the reason
why we find people that we have lost,
and have been separated from us
for a long time.
You're really profound.
Why is she there?
Where did she get the money?
Federico, don't be like that.
Let's call her tomorrow.
She will explain tomorrow.
- No. Let's go.
- No, stop.
I might trip.
Another glass of wine, please.
Antonia... that's enough.
Why?
Are you scared that I will make a scene here?
Are you ashamed to be here with me?
Antonia, please.
I chose you,
that's why I won't leave your side.
Let's stop fooling around here, Nero.
You're here with me
because you have no choice.
Because even though you chose me,
my heart wouldn't be hurting now.
Fresh air?
Yes.
I'm sorry if I bothered you.
It's fine.
The space is huge.
There's enough space for both of us.
I'm just not used to places
with lots of people.
Besides, I don't think
there's proper ventilation inside.
We're probably breathing each other's breath.
Right!
But I don't want to bother you anymore.
I don't want to ruin your privacy.
I'll leave you to it.
Thank you.
Can I call?
Sorry, someone sent a message.
Sorry, you can't.
I'm at an event
and there's a pest standing beside me.
I'm also attending an event,
and there's a pest by my side.
To be fair, my pest is dressed well.
Really? What is the pest wearing?
He is wearing a maroon and white suit.
To be honest, the pest standing beside me
is cute in her dress.
She's wearing a light green dress.
You're Ninja Copy Girl?
Where is Lina?
There she is.
Girl, where did you go?
I just went out to get some fresh air.
Well, guess what,
we're now at the exciting part.
Yes.
What are you up to?
What are you two planning?
Just trust us girl, it will be fun.
Exactly, as in super.
Super.
Maybe that's something foolish.
Of course not.
Babycakes, come on!
- No!
- Come on, Baby.
No!
You're such a killjoy.
Come on, cheers.
Hello, hello!
Good evening, Gyronella University!
Oh my goodness, this is it.
We're now here at the exciting part
of our Grand Ball.
As if it couldn't get even grander.
In fact, our theme is Return to Kindness,
right?
And so, Ms. Camille Villarico and Aira Rivera
thought of a way so we can raise more funds
and can help more people.
And we call this,
Auction for the Greater Good.
Well anyway, you might ask me,
how can we do this?
So, we will present here an item or a prize,
and of course,
everyone here has a chance to put on a bid.
But of course, the highest bidder
will be winning that prize.
So are you guys ready?
Are your wallets ready?
- Yeah!
- Okay, seems like it.
So, let's call on our first prize,
or rather the first prize holder,
Mr. Tristan Ferell.
Are you going to be auctioned? Just kidding.
Anyway, what item do you have, Tristan?
I have two tickets to a BTS Concert in Seoul.
Oh my God.
Who wants to go?
Wow.
I think a lot of people want to go with you.
Let's go, Baby!
Not now, maybe later.
I'll think about it.
So let's start the bidding,
let's get it rolling.
Yes?
20,000 pesos.
20,000 immediately from the girl on Table 3!
Do we hear a 30?
30,000 pesos.
Wow.
30,000 from the girl on Table 5!
Oh yes, Camille?
Yes, 250,000 pesos.
Wow, GU is just shocked right now.
That's a big jump.
Okay, that's 250,000 pesos
for two tickets to BTS Concert
with Mr. Tristan Ferell,
sold to Ms. Camille Villarico!
Lower! Lower! Lower!
- Go, Baby!
- Lower!
- Cakes!
- Go, Baby!
- Lower!
- Cakes!
- Go, Baby!
Go, Baby! Cakes!
- Cakes!
Go, Baby!
350,000 pesos!
- Oh my God!
If I'm not mistaken,
350,000 pesos from Ms. Aira Rivera.
So, that famed Chef Jiro
will be cooking you dinner
with Mr. Aldus Ferell.
So oh, oh, congratulations!
Wow, we're raising so many funds tonight, GU.
So...
what's your plan?
I don't know too.
Just tell her the truth.
Do you think it's that easy?
It looks like they're having fun in the ball.
You can go back now.
How about you?
I already called my driver.
I just want to go home.
Are you sure?
Why?
Do you want me to change my mind?
Because I'm only generous for a few minutes.
Go back, Nero.
Go to her.
Win her back.
Win Florence back.
So now, may I call on for our next item,
Ms. Florence Dela Cruz?
Yes, come on down.
For this item, Florence will be
cooking you a private dinner
in a set-up by the beach.
So, Ms. Florence... Come join me.
Go, Florence.
You're being called on stage.
- Come on, just go.
- Let's give Florence a round of applause.
Go now.
- A round of applause.
- Come on, just go.
Go now.
Ms. Dela Cruz, thanks for joining us.
So, for everyone's information,
Ms. Florence is the student representative
of the Com Arts Department.
And they are responsible for
hosting our ball this evening.
And she is also very sporting to participate
in our Auction for the Greater Good,
so thank you.
And of course, all funds raised
will be donated to charity.
Ms. Florence, you know what?
I heard you're a very good cook.
Is that right?
I haven't poisoned anyone, so... I think yes?
Sometimes,
I don't get the humor of poor people,
but anyway, let's get this bidding started.
Private dinner cooked by Ms. Florence.
Anyone?
50,000 pesos.
Babycakes, who is that guy?
I have no idea.
In fairness with Ms. Florence,
she's a box office hit.
Yes, a lot of people are bidding.
Maybe that's because
Florence brings the hope of love.
And whoever sees her beauty,
will overcome everything just to achieve it.
He's wasted.
He's already drunk.
- I support her.
- Quiet, all of you!
This is the continuation of the story.
Can you please...
Beautiful.
- Anyone?
- Florence!
One million pesos.
One million p-pesos?
That's a lot of feeding programs,
in that case.
So, anyone?
And if any of you are planning to outbid me,
don't try anymore.
Because I won't waste this chance
to be with an important person to me.
I won't waste the chance
to be with you again, Florence.
Florence!
Florence, wait!
Nero, please, leave me alone.
Okay, but it's cold here...
What are you doing?
Are you playing a prank on me, Nero?
Are you playing with me?
What do you think of me, a doll?
Your toy car?
- No.
- No?
And what went into your mind earlier?
Why did you make a bid?
Didn't you even think how Antonia would feel?
Antonia and I are over.
So you called it quits again,
so now, you're going after me?
What?
You'll use me again to make her jealous?
That's it?
Have you forgotten what you told me?
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
Nero, I don't want this anymore.
I don't want to expect. I don't want to hope.
I don't want to open my heart to you,
because it hurts.
It hurts when you make a mistake
and believe that it's for real.
So, please...
Don't play with my heart.
I'm sorry.
Florence? What happened?
Is there a problem?
Grandfather...
Stop crying, my grandchild.
Dude, you have to relax.
Grandfather is mad.
Florence is missing,
so don't add to his problem.
It's Nero's fault.
He's acting as if he controls everything.
Are you mad at Nero because he's being Nero?
Or you're mad at him
because Florence likes him?
Look, dude... it's too complicated.
If I'm being honest,
you should both stop pursuing Florence.
It's you who said that Florence is our cook,
and it's not good to see
that both Ferells are fighting because of her.
That's the problem with both of you.
You don't care about
how each other would feel.
Sit together and talk.
Man-to-man, from one Ferell to another.
Imagine, what would people think
if they find out
that you and Owen are fighting over her?
I don't care what others would say.
My God, dude, you're both Ferells.
Have you forgotten what Grandfather said?
That if we, Ferells, have a problem,
we fix it, together.
That's right. Just fix that problem.
The last thing we want
is us to tearing each other apart
because of Florence.
Hello, Serafica.
Is Florence there?
She's not back yet, Don Ferell.
But the boys are here already.
Call me once Florence is back.
Are you sure about this?
If Florence did walk home,
this is the nearest route
going back to the mansion.
But Don Ferell,
we've been driving around
for quite some time.
Why don't we call her parents,
Lydia and Federico?
Maybe she went home to them.
Hello?
Garpidio.
Rogelio, we have an emergency here.
Can we just talk tomorrow?
Is this about your cook named Florence?
You don't have to worry. Florence is here.
The kid will spend the night here.
But don't worry, she's safe here.
She was crying earlier.
She's probably safe here...
away from your grandsons,
whose relationship is a bit complicated
with her.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Goodnight, Garpidio.
Let's go home, Dencio.
Okay.
The wealth of the Almeros is something else.
I wonder where Grandfather Roger is?
She's my daughter-in-law.
Her name's Alyanna.
Are you okay, Florence?
Yes. I'm doing okay.
Let's have breakfast.
I'm sure you're hungry now.
No, thank you.
I'll go ahead first, Grandfather Roger.
Are you sure?
Yes, and I'm so embarrassed,
I've caused you so much trouble.
And I'm also thinking about Grandfather Garp.
- I'll ask the driver to take you home.
- No need.
You've done so much for me.
I'll just take the tricycle home.
All right.
Well, if there's anything you need...
you are welcome in this house, Florence.
Thank you, Grandfather Roger.
It was nice meeting you.
Good Morning, Gyronella University.
And we are back to regular programming.
After the Grand GU Ball last night,
it's officially the morning after,
and I know a lot of my followers out there
are excited to know
the highlights from last night.
That's because a lot of things happened,
like, a lot of people were trying
to outshine others.
A lot of people took it to the next level.
And actually, I think there was fighting too.
And we also would want to know
who was the standout, and...
well, let's just say,
those who slightly made a mark.
But before we proceed to our rundown,
let me welcome our special guest for today.
And to be honest,
I didn't expect to see this person
at the Grand GU Ball last night.
Let us all welcome, Aristotle Rah Cortez.
Hello, Ash.
And hello to the listeners of GU TV.
- Thanks, Aristotle.
- Of course.
And you know,
you coming to the Grand GU Ball last night
is like one of the highlights
of our evening, right?
And I just want to know,
how did you get to the Grand GU Ball,
considering that you come
from the rival university,
which is Denison University.
Well, to be honest, even with us in Denison,
we look forward to
the Grand Ball of Gyronella.
But in all honesty,
we always felt like the event
is a bit excessive.
Symptomatic of what is wrong in our country.
Imagine, real people,
I mean rich people partying,
unmindful of the things
happening in our country.
But last night, my eyes were open,
and it's not just about rich kids partying.
Because last night was also
about raising funds,
so there's something you can give
the underserved communities.
I will be honest, I am truly impressed.
And I'm starting to think
that Gyronella is the better school.
Well, to be fair,
it wasn't always like this in our university,
but thank you to the efforts
of our new student
and the representative
of Com Arts Department,
Ms. Florence Dela Cruz.
Grandfather Garp?
Florence is back, guys.
You got us worried.
Yeah. Did you enjoy your night out?
Night out?
Maybe I just got tired,
that's why I fell asleep
in the Almero's mansion.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
By the way,
can you please return this to Camille?
It's so expensive, I might lose and ruin it.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you. You're the best.
Don Ferell, here are the people
you called for.
You didn't tell us
that the people you're cooking for
are young men.
All this while, I thought Don Ferell's
grandsons are kindergarteners.
But Don Ferell already explained to us
your situation with Nero and Owen.
Florence, it's not a good situation.
That's why your father and I have decided
that you'll stop cooking for this household.
But, Mother, it's a pity if I let go of the...
What? You're thinking about the salary?
Do you think I'd be at peace
knowing that you're cooking
for young men who are falling for you?
But we're still thankful to Don Ferell,
because he said he'll continue
giving you a scholarship.
As for the extra income,
don't worry about that Florence,
because we have found a new job.
There's a caterer who'll hire us
as a regular staff
to make their pastries.
That's enough for your father's medication
and your schooling.
And perfect timing because
it's your semester break.
We'll be able to save up
for your next semester.
I understand, Father.
I'm sorry.
Come on, pack your things.
We're leaving.
Just understand your father.
He's just worried about you.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Let's go.
Girls, look at this.
South Korean trip booking
is confirmed, right?
Tristan, I am so excited
for our South Korean trip.
Annyeong haseyo. Kamsa hamnida.
Let me remind you, Camille, it's not a date.
We'll go there to watch BTS,
and I'll be there
to appreciate Jung Kook's greatness.
Of course, me too.
I'm definitely there for the music.
If you want extracurricular activities,
I'm willing and able.
Curricular?
Yeah, you know,
cultural immersion
and a tour of the Gyeongbokgung palace,
something like that.
How about you, Aldus?
Have you packed already
for our trip to Japan?
Yeah.
And aside from our date with Chef Jiro,
do you have other plans?
First, it's not a date.
What you won in the auction
is a treat from me
to eat from the best sushi chef in the world.
And second,
after our dinner date with Chef Jiro,
we're on our own in Tokyo.
You're such a snob.
How about you, Lina?
What's your plan for this academic break?
Me?
I'll just stay at home.
Maybe the truth is
you'll be flirting with Troy.
- Of course not.
- No, no, no.
Why are you both defensive?
True.
And we all know,
you guys are both
negativity-charged particles.
And if Newton is correct,
you will always repel each other.
And why does it seem like
the Ferells are hot-tempered?
Yes, if they're not hot-tempered,
they're moody.
Is there a problem at home?
Troy, Tristan, and Aldus
are discreetly exchanging
knowing looks with each other.
It seems they're hiding something.
Looks like there's a problem at home.
It's Florence.
To some extent, also Owen.
Why? What happened?
Florence is gone.
She resigned as the cook in the mansion.
What?
We will miss you so much.
Mr. Dencio...
are you crying?
Don't cry.
You can visit me.
Bring all of them during your day off.
Me, crying?
I'm not a crybaby.
Be patient with Dencio, he cries easily.
Yesterday, he kept on crying
because the sunshine is beautiful.
It was really beautiful.
Mr. Dencio, you're something else.
I'll treasure the times
I was here in the mansion
with all of you.
In the short time we were together,
I learned a lot of things from all of you.
And I became a better person
because I met all of you.
Stop. Please go.
You'll really make us all cry.
Go ahead.
Let's do a group hug first.
Bye.
You take care, okay?
So do you think Nero
will try to win her back?
This is exciting.
I hope they patch things up,
and I hope they'll end up together.
So there'll be a sequel to this story.
When I thought
that letting go would be difficult,
but the truth is,
I seem to be coping pretty well.
That's good.
You act like I'm the only broken-hearted one.
What about you?
I can't believe that girl.
The audacity to show herself to us
after what she did to Florence.
She's using her charms again to trap Owen.
Lina, why don't you keep an eye on Owen?
I think you two will be perfect together.
Yes.
Good morning, Mother!
Good morning, Father!
Good Morning, Florence.
What are you doing here?
Florence, he's been waiting here
for quite some time.
He said you owe him a dinner,
because in the auction,
he bid one million for you to cook for him.
Is that true?